

SANN CHESDA

#155Eo, Monorum, 7 Makara, Phnom Penh sannchesda8981@gmail.com · +85577585344 (Telegram)

I am a graduate from Limkokwing University of Phnom Penh with a strong educational background and a passion for continuous learning. With experience in the government and real estate industry, I have developed valuable skills in my field. My passion for exploring new things, particularly in technology, keeps my mind stimulated. Additionally, I enjoy adventurous activities to maintain a fresh perspective.

EXPERIENCE

JULY 2021 – FEBRUARY 2023

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, MINISTRY OF POSTS AND TELECOMMUNICATIONS

HRMIS Mobile App

This application serves as an extension of the existing web application, functioning as a user-friendly information portal specifically designed for government officials to effortlessly access vital information.

- Build and design the flow of app with **Flutter** using GetX
- Integrate with existing API

eLearning Platform

Nationwide eLearning platform for students, teachers, government officials, and citizens that consist of a Content Management System (CMS) and a Learning Management System (LMS).

- Integrate both websites using SSO from WSO2
- Setup and customize the CMS (WordPress) with new features
- Setup and customize the LMS (Moodle) with iOMAD
- Setup and config server with load balancer for production using CentOS and Nginx

Office of the Council of Ministers

A small-scale mobile app provides easy accessibility for viewing documents of current and past meetings, while also offering user authentication for the corresponding web application.

- Design UI/UX and Prototype using Figma
- Lead a mobile team to build the mobile using **Flutter**
- Integrate with Mekong Net SMS and Firebase Remote Config

MARCH 2023 – JULY 2023

FLUTTER MOBILE DEVELOPER, POINTER PROPERTY CO, LTD

Pointer Estate

Property owners effortlessly provide feedbacks on their properties, receive announcements, and conveniently make bill payments through ABA Pay, KHQR, and Visa Cards.

- Build using Flutter and GetX with Collaboration with UI/UX designer
- Integrate with Firebase Remote Config, ABA Payway, Sentry, Mixpanel

Pointer Marketplace

A mobile app that lists all available property with the best price. Furthermore, user can book a visit from their mobile app easily with the company agent.

- Build using Flutter and Riverpod
- Integrate Google Maps, Firebase remote config, Sentry

EDUCATION

NOVEMBER 2017 – JULY 2021

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, LIMKOKWING UNIVERSITY OF CREATIVE TECHNOLOGY

- C++ programming 1 & 2 Object Oriented Programming
- iOS & Android Mobile Development
- Software Design Database Design & Management
- Build an iOS application with Cloud Firestore and Swift
- Build an e-commerce Android application with Cloud Firestore and Java
- Average GPA: 3.85

JULY 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

ARROW DOT HARDWARE PROGRAMMING

- Arduino Programming
- Processing IDE with Java Programming

SKILLS

- Hybrid Mobile Application (Flutter & Dart)
- Static Website (HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap)
- Web Application (Laravel with Blade, Nodejs with ejs)
- Hardware Programming (Arduino)
- Native Mobile Application (Java & Android, iOS & Swift & Storyboard)
- Desktop Application (C++, Java)

- Firebase (Firestore, Authentication, Remote Config, Storage)
- Marketing Analytic tools (Segment & Mixpanel)
- Open-Source Web Application (WordPress, Moodle)
- Linux (CentOS or Ubuntu with Nginx)
- Crash Reporting tool (Sentry)

ACTIVITIES

- Music: Listening to music and playing guitar
- Camping: Seeing nature and exploring
- Cycling: Group cycling with friends
- Learning: Always explore new technology



https://sannchesda.github.io/portfolio/